Using Language Reading and Discussing
Come and Eat Here 2
A week later, Vang Pong's restaurant was nearly full and he felt happier.
Perhaps he would be able to earn his living after all and not have to close his restaurant.
He did not look forward to being in debt because his restaurant was no longer popular.
She did not look happy but glared at him.
May I ask what you were doing in my restaurant the other day?
I thought you were a new customer and now I know that you only came to spy on me
and my menu," she shouted.
Please excuse me," he calmly explained, "
I wanted to know where all my customers had gone last week.
I followed one of them and found them in your restaurant.’
I don’t want to upset you,
but I found your menu so limited that I stopped worrying and started advertising the benefits of my food.
Yes," he added, "and I would miss my dumplings and fatty pork.
Don’t you get tired quickly?
But don’t you think it would be better if you were a bit thinner?
I’m sure you’d feel much healthier." They began to talk about menus
and balanced diets.
They served raw vegetables with the hamburgers and boiled the potatoes rather than frying them.
They served fresh fruit with the ice cream.
After some time the two found that their business cooperation had turned into a personal one.
Finally they got married and lived happily ever after.